Roseph Darl Tungul

Instructor | Web Developer



About Me

I'm a freelance Web Developer and part-time Instructor in the Philippines with over 4 years of experience. I create and design one-of-akind websites and applications that are not found in any template.

Contact Information



+63-9381430222



rosephdarl@gmail.com



https://rdtungul.github.io/



99 San Nicolas 1st, Sasmuan, Pampanga, Philippines

Professional Skills

Coding Languages/Frameworks:

HTML5/SEO, CSS3/SCSS, JavaScript/ES6, PHP, MySQL, React/Redux, Node/NPM, MongoDB, WebPack, API, JEST, Python, Git, etc.

Libraries/Plugins:

Bootstrap 5, Tailwind, Material UI, WordPress, Elementor Pro, ACF Pro, Astra Pro, Gutenberg. SiteGround, TablePress, WooCommerce, Shopify, LearnDash, MailChimp, Heroku, etc.

Software Applications:

Figma, Adobe XD, Illustrator, Photoshop, Kajabi, WebFlow, InDesign, Premiere Pro, FileZilla, Airtable, Asana, ConceptBoard, etc.

Character References

Michael P. Maglanque MBA, MIT

Dean at College of Business Administration Email: netad@gnc.edu.ph

Justine G. Vinuya, MBA

Academic Instructor Email: justinegvinuya@gmail.com

Educational Backgound

(2015-2018)

GUAGUA NATIONAL COLLEGES

Bachelor of Science in Information Technology

(2019-2020)

GUAGUA NATIONAL COLLEGES

Bachelor of Science in Secondary Education

(2020 - Present)

GUAGUA NATIONAL COLLEGES

Master in Business Administration

Work Experiences

(Oct. 2017 - Jan. 2018)

Beepo, Inc. - Clark, Pampanga, Philippines

WEB DEVELOPER / GRAPHIC DESIGNER / VIDEO EDITOR (ON-THE-JOB TRAINING)

(Apr. 2021 - Sept. 2021)

Pegasaas - Victoria, BC, Canada

TECHNICAL SUPPORT

- WordPress Plugin Development (Web Performance)
- Front-end/Backend Development
- Content Witing

(Jan. 2022 - Aug. 2022)

Easy Web Leads - Sydney, Australia

WORDPRESS DEVELOPER

- Front-end/Backend Development
- · Graphic Design

(May 2018 - Present)

Guagua National Colleges

ACADEMIC INSTRUCTOR

- Web Development/Web Design
- · Cisco Instructor
- Capstone/Research
- Software Engineering

These are the websites on which I've worked on both Front-end and Backend development:

- https://talostone.com.au/
- https://edenlaserclinics.com.au/
- waterlessurinalcartridges.com.au
- https://needmorestorage.com.au/
- https://cabinetsexpress.com.au/ • http://envirotech.com.au/
- https://www.cresi.ca/
- https://anna.asn.au/
- http://gnc.edu.ph/